Mello, Michael; Papers apap287
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Research Files, 1800-2004; 7; 14 cubic ft.
  - "The Dissenting Opinion- Its Use and Abuse" by Evan A. Evans, 1938 (Box 5 (7-Research Files), Folder 3)
  - "Dissenting Opinion- Cornell Law Quarterly", 1959 (Box 5 (7-Research Files), Folder 4)
  - "The Dissenting Opinions of Mr. Justice Daniel" by H.B. Brown, 1887 (Box 5 (7-Research Files), Folder 5)
  - "The Dissenting Opinions of Mr. Justice Harlan" by H.B. Brown, 1912 (Box 5 (7-Research Files), Folder 6)
  - "Dissent and Stare Decisis in the Supreme Court", 1940 (Box 5 (7-Research Files), Folder 7)
  - "The Dissent that Telegraphs", Undated (Box 5 (7-Research Files), Folder 8)
  - "Division of Opinion in the Supreme Court: A History of Judicial Disintegration" by Karl M. ZoBelt, 1959 (Box 5 (7-Research Files), Folder 9)
  - "Divorce Mediation: A Feminist Perpective" by Martha Shaffer, 1988 (Box 5 (7-Research Files), Folder 10)
  - "Do we have an Unwritten Constitution?" by Thomas C. Grey, 1975 (Box 5 (7-Research Files), Folder 11)
  - "Do We Need a Philosophy of Law?" by Roscoe Pound, 1905 (Box 5 (7-Research Files), Folder 12)
  - "The Doctrine of Stare Decisis" by E.M. Wise, 1975 (Box 5 (7-Research Files), Folder 13)
  - Doe v. LaBrosse, 1991 (Box 5 (7-Research Files), Folder 14)
  - Douglas- Consistent Dissents, Undated (Box 5 (7-Research Files), Folder 15)
  - Douglas v. Florida, 1991 (Box 5 (7-Research Files), Folder 16)
  - Draft Rules for Appointments of Counsel in Federal Death Penalty Cases, Eastern and Southern Districts of New York, 1992 (Box 5 (7-Research Files), Folder 17)
  - Drinking Age Report ( 1 of 2), 1987 (Box 5 (7-Research Files), Folder 18)
  - Drinking Age Report ( 2 of 2), 1987 (Box 5 (7-Research Files), Folder 19)
  - Drug Laws, 1988 (Box 5 (7-Research Files), Folder 20)
  - Eddings v. Oklahoma, 1982 (Box 5 (7-Research Files), Folder 21)
  - Editorials and Letters to the Editor Regarding the Juvenile Death Penalty, 1987-1988; Undated (Box 5 (7-Research Files), Folder 22)
  - Elledge v. Dugger, 1987 (Box 5 (7-Research Files), Folder 23)
  - "The Emergence of Feminist Jurisprudence: An Essay" by Ann C. Scales, 1986 (Box 5 (7-Research Files), Folder 24)
  - "Equality and Feminist Legal Theory" by Christine A. Littlebon, 1987 (Box 5 (7-Research Files), Folder 25)
  - Evidence Outside Record Impermissible, 1851; 1966; 1969-1970 (Box 5 (7-Research Files), Folder 26)
  - "Excluded Voices: New Voices in the Legal Profession Making New Voices in the Law" by Carrie Menkel-Meadow, 1987 (Box 5 (7-Research Files), Folder 27)
  - Execution of Mentally Retarded Persons Under S.66001 A. 8963, 1990 (Box 5 (7-Research Files), Folder 28)
  - Execution in the United States in 2004, 2004 January (Box 5 (7-Research Files), Folder 29)
  - "Execution of Whites for Crimes Against Blacks: Execptions to the Rule?" by Michael Radelet, 1989 (Box 5 (7-Research Files), Folder 30)
  - Executions Scheduled for 2004 (Box 5 (7-Research Files), Folder 31)
  - Exonerations by State 1973- Present, 2004 (Box 5 (7-Research Files), Folder 32)
  - "Experimental Analysis: A Contribution to Feminist Research" by Sholamit Reinharz, ca. 1983 (Box 5 (7-Research Files), Folder 33)
  - "Expert Services in the Defense of Criminal Case: The Constitutional and Stationary Rights of Indigents" by John F. Decker, 1982 (Box 5 (7-Research Files), Folder 34)
  - "An Extension of the Rights of Access: The Pro Se Litigant's Right to the Notification of the Requirements of the Summary Judgement Rule" by Joseph M. McLaughlin, 1987 (Box 5 (7-Research Files), Folder 35)
  - Facing the Death Penalty Edited by Michael Radelet-Giarratano Chapter, 1989 (Box 5 (7-Research Files), Folder 36)
  - Barry Lee Fairchild, 1990 (Box 5 (7-Research Files), Folder 37)
  - Felker v. Turpin, 1996 May 17 (Box 5 (7-Research Files), Folder 38)
  - Federal Cases of Interest, 1992 (Box 5 (7-Research Files), Folder 39)
  - The Federal Penalty Act of 1989 (Box 5 (7-Research Files), Folder 40)
  - Federal Death Penalty Cases: Recommendations Concerning the Cost and Quality of Defense Representation- Subcommitee on Federal Death Penalty Cases, Committee on Defender Services, Judicial Conference of the United States, 1998 (Box 5 (7-Research Files), Folder 41)
  - Federal Expenditures by State for FYI, 1992; 1993 (Box 5 (7-Research Files), Folder 42)
  - Federal Habeas Corpus Practice and Procedure: 1991 Cumulative Supplement by Liebman and Goldstein, ca. 1991 (Box 5 (7-Research Files), Folder 43)
  - Federal Hitchcock Cases, 1988 (Box 5 (7-Research Files), Folder 44)
  - "Feminism and Legal Method: The Difference it Makes" by Mary Jane Mossman, 1987 (Box 5 (7-Research Files), Folder 45)
  - "Feminism, Epistemology and the Rhetoric of Law: Reading Bowen v. Gillard" by A.W. Phinney III, 1989 (Box 5 (7-Research Files), Folder 46)
  - "Feminist Disclosure, Moral Values, and the Law- A Conservation" by Marcos et. al- The 1984 James McCormick Mitchell Leture, 1985 (Box 5 (7-Research Files), Folder 47)
  - Feminist Jurisprudence Articles, Undated (Box 5 (7-Research Files), Folder 48)
  - "Feminist Jurisprudence: Illusion or Reality?" by Margaret Thornton, 1986 (Box 5 (7-Research Files), Folder 49)
  - Fenemore v. US, 1797 (Box 5 (7-Research Files), Folder 50)
  - Final Report of the National Commission on Reform of Federal Criminal Laws- Chapter 36, Sentencing of Death of Life Imprisonment, 1971 (Box 5 (7-Research Files), Folder 51)
  - "Financing the Right to Counsel in Capital Cases" by Michael Millman, 1985 (Box 5 (7-Research Files), Folder 52)
  - "The First Decade of the Supreme Court of the United States" by Charles Warren, 1940 (Box 5 (7-Research Files), Folder 53)
  - Fletcher v. Peck, 1810 (Box 5 (7-Research Files), Folder 54)
  - Florida Cases Finding Hitchcock error harmless, 1990 (Box 5 (7-Research Files), Folder 55)
  - Florida Supreme Court Capital Case Decisions, 1988-1989 (Box 5 (7-Research Files), Folder 56)
  - Florida Supreme Court Capital Case Decisions, 1993 (Box 5 (7-Research Files), Folder 57)
  - Florida v. Pitts, 1970 (Box 5 (7-Research Files), Folder 58)
  - "For Jurisprudential Sociology" by Philippe Nonet, 1976 (Box 5 (7-Research Files), Folder 59)
  - "For What It's Worth" by Steven L. Winter, 1992 (Box 5 (7-Research Files), Folder 60)
  - James A. Ford, 1987 (Box 5 (7-Research Files), Folder 61)
  - "The Forked Path of Dissent" by Maurice Kelman, 1986 (Box 5 (7-Research Files), Folder 62)
  - "Form and Function in the Administration of Justice: The Bill of Rights and Federal Habeas Corpus" by Larry Yackle, 1990 (Box 5 (7-Research Files), Folder 63)
  - "Four theories of Precedent and its Role in Judicial Decisions" by James G. Gisenhower III, 1988 (Box 5 (7-Research Files), Folder 64)
  - Francis v. Spraggins, 1983 (Box 5 (7-Research Files), Folder 65)
  - Franklin v. Lynavgh, 1987-1988 (Box 5 (7-Research Files), Folder 66)
  - Frazier v. Garrison IS.D., 1993 (Box 5 (7-Research Files), Folder 67)
  - "Freedom and Constraint in Adjudication" by Duncan Kennedy, 1986 (Box 5 (7-Research Files), Folder 68)
  - "The Function of Comparative Law" by Pierre Lepaulle, 1922 (Box 5 (7-Research Files), Folder 69)
  - The Gallup Report- "The Death Penalty", 1986 (Box 5 (7-Research Files), Folder 70)
  - "Gender and Jurisprudence: An Agenda for Research" by Deborah L. Rhode, 1987 (Box 5 (7-Research Files), Folder 71)
  - Georgia Statute- Juveniles, 1986; Undated (Box 5 (7-Research Files), Folder 72)
  - Georgia Supreme Court- Juveniles, 1988 (Box 5 (7-Research Files), Folder 73)
  - Glock v. Singletary, 1992 (Box 5 (7-Research Files), Folder 74)
  - Godfrey v. Georgia, 1979 (Box 5 (7-Research Files), Folder 75)
  - Goodie v. Wainwright, 1984 (Box 6 (7-Research Files), Folder 1)
  - Gorham v. Florida, 1988 (Box 6 (7-Research Files), Folder 2)
  - Gosch v. Collins, 1993 (Box 6 (7-Research Files), Folder 3)
  - Goss v. Lopez, 1975 (Box 6 (7-Research Files), Folder 4)
  - Gary Graham, 1988; 1992 (Box 6 (7-Research Files), Folder 5)
  - Green v. Zant, Undated (Box 6 (7-Research Files), Folder 6)
  - Grossman v. Florida, 1988 (Box 6 (7-Research Files), Folder 7)
  - Grove City, 1980-1986 (Box 6 (7-Research Files), Folder 8)
  - Grove City, 1980-1986 (Box 6 (7-Research Files), Folder 9)
  - Grove City, 1980-1986 (Box 6 (7-Research Files), Folder 10)
  - Grove City Legislation, 1984-1988 (Box 6 (7-Research Files), Folder 11)
  - Grove City Legislation, 1984-1988; Undated (Box 6 (7-Research Files), Folder 12)
  - Guaranteed Student Loan and Civil Rights Enforcement, 1982 (Box 6 (7-Research Files), Folder 13)
  - Guardians Assn. v. Civil Serv. Comm'n NYC, 1983 (Box 6 (7-Research Files), Folder 14)
  - "Habeus Corpus as a Safety Value for Intelligence" by Bruce Ledewitz, Undated (Box 6 (7-Research Files), Folder 15)
  - HAC- Model Agrument for FSC briefs on the direct appeal, 1989 (Box 6 (7-Research Files), Folder 16)
  - Hall v. DeCuir, 1877 (Box 6 (7-Research Files), Folder 17)
  - Handbook of Existing Rules Pertaining to Human Rights in the Inter-American System, 1985 (Box 6 (7-Research Files), Folder 18)
  - Hayburn, 1792 (Box 6 (7-Research Files), Folder 19)
  - Hearst v. US, 1981 (Box 6 (7-Research Files), Folder 20)
  - Highway Safety Legislation, 1986; Undated (Box 6 (7-Research Files), Folder 21)
  - Hill v. Florida, 1995 (Box 6 (7-Research Files), Folder 22)
  - History of the Death Penalty in New York, 1991; 1994-1995 (Box 6 (7-Research Files), Folder 23)
  - Hitchcock Error Cases, 1987 (Box 6 (7-Research Files), Folder 24)
  - Hitchcock Error Cases, 1988 (Box 6 (7-Research Files), Folder 25)
  - Hitchcock Error Cases, 1989 (Box 6 (7-Research Files), Folder 26)
  - Hitchcock Error Cases, 1991 (Box 6 (7-Research Files), Folder 27)
  - "Holmes and Brandeis: Libertarian and Republic Justifications for Free Speech" by Pnina Lahav, 1988 (Box 6 (7-Research Files), Folder 28)
  - "Holmes: His First Amendment Theory and His Pragmatist Bent" by Edward J. Bloustein, 1988 (Box 6 (7-Research Files), Folder 29)
  - Holsworth v. Florida, 1988 (Box 6 (7-Research Files), Folder 30)
  - Hooks v. Wainwright, 1982; 1985 (Box 6 (7-Research Files), Folder 31)
  - House of Representatives Congressional Record, 1988 (Box 6 (7-Research Files), Folder 32)
  - House v. Balkcom, 1984 (Box 6 (7-Research Files), Folder 33)
  - "How goes the Supreme Court?" by William J. Brennan, JR., 1985 (Box 6 (7-Research Files), Folder 34)
  - "How to do What We Want to do: Thoughts about Feminist Methodology" by Renate Duelli Klein, ca. 1983 (Box 6 (7-Research Files), Folder 35)
  - "The Human Dimension in Appellate Judging: A Brief Reflection on a Timeless Concern" by Judith S. Kaye, 1988 (Box 6 (7-Research Files), Folder 36)
  - "Humane Law and Humanistic Justice" by Edward de Grazia, 1988 (Box 6 (7-Research Files), Folder 37)
  - "Humanizing the Criminal Process: Some Decisions of Mr. Justice Marshall" by David L. Bazelon, 1978 (Box 6 (7-Research Files), Folder 38)
  - "The Idea of a Commutarian Morality" by Philip Selznick, 1987 (Box 6 (7-Research Files), Folder 39)
  - "Imposing the Death Penalty on Juvenile Murders: A Constitutional Assessment" by Dome and Gewerth, 1991 (Box 7 (7-Research Files), Folder 1)
  - Imposition of Death Sentences For Juvenile Offenses, January 1, 1982, Through June 24, 1988 by Victor L. Streib (Box 7 (7-Research Files), Folder 2)
  - "In Defense of Dissents" by William J.Brennan, JR., 1986 (Box 7 (7-Research Files), Folder 3)
  - In Forma Libris, Undated (Box 7 (7-Research Files), Folder 4)
  - "In Memoriam- Law Day Address at the University of Texas: The Enlightened Jurisprudence of Justice Thurgood Marshall" by William Wayne Justice, 1993 (Box 7 (7-Research Files), Folder 5)
  - "In Search of a Feminist Jurisprudence" by Christine A. Littleton, 1987 (Box 7 (7-Research Files), Folder 6)
  - "In Your Court: State Judicial Federalism in Capital Cases" by Wright & Miller, 1986 (Box 7 (7-Research Files), Folder 7)
  - Index of Hitchcock Cases, Undated (Box 7 (7-Research Files), Folder 8)
  - "The Indigent Accused, The Psychiatrist, and the Insanity Defense" by Goldstein and Fine, 1962 (Box 7 (7-Research Files), Folder 9)
  - "The Indigent Criminal Defendant and Defense Services: A Search for Constitutional Standards" by Margolin and Wagner, 1973 (Box 7 (7-Research Files), Folder 10)
  - "The Indigent's Right to an Adequate Defense: Expert and Investigational Assistancein Criminal Proceedings", 1970 (Box 7 (7-Research Files), Folder 11)
  - Ingraham v. Wright, 1977 (Box 7 (7-Research Files), Folder 12)
  - "Innocence and Affirmative Action" by Thomas Ross, 1990 (Box 7 (7-Research Files), Folder 13)
  - Innocence and the Death Penalty: Assesssing the Danger of Mistaken Executions- Staff Report by the Subcommittee on Civil and Constitutional Rights, Committee on the Judiciary, 1993 (Box 7 (7-Research Files), Folder 14)
  - The Insanity Defense by Abraham Goldstein- Excerpt, 1967 (Box 7 (7-Research Files), Folder 15)
  - Inter-American Commission on Human Rights- Resolution N 3/87, Case N9647, 1987 (Box 7 (7-Research Files), Folder 16)
  - International Human Rights Treaties- Hearings Before the Committee on Foreign Relations- United States Senate, 1979 (Box 7 (7-Research Files), Folder 17)
  - Interpretation of Judiciary Law 35-B, S125.27, 1995 (Box 7 (7-Research Files), Folder 18)
  - The Invisibility of Women in Labor Law: Gender- Neutrality in Model-Building" by Joanne Conoghan, 1986 (Box 7 (7-Research Files), Folder 19)
  - "It is Mitigation or Aggravation? Troublesome Areas of Defense Evidence in Capital Sentencing" by Deana Dorman Logan, 1989 (Box 7 (7-Research Files), Folder 20)
  - Sonia Jacobs, 1990-1991 (Box 7 (7-Research Files), Folder 21)
  - "John Marshall Harlan", 1987 (Box 7 (7-Research Files), Folder 22)
  - "John Marshall Harlan: A Justice Neglected" by Henry J. Abraham, 1955 (Box 7 (7-Research Files), Folder 23)
  - Marvin Edwin Johnson, 1989 (Box 7 (7-Research Files), Folder 24)
  - Terrell M. Johnson, 1993 (Box 7 (7-Research Files), Folder 25)
  - Johnson v. Mississippi, 1988 (Box 7 (7-Research Files), Folder 26)
  - The Journal of the National Prison Project, Summer, 1987 (Box 7 (7-Research Files), Folder 27)
  - "The Judgement Intuitive: the Function of the 'Hunch' in Judicial Decisions" by Joseph C. Hutcheson, Jr., 1982 (Box 7 (7-Research Files), Folder 28)
  - "Judicial Obligation, Precedent and the Common Land" by Stephen R. Perry, 1987 (Box 7 (7-Research Files), Folder 29)
  - "Judicial Review and the Rights and Laws of Nature" by Walter Berns, 1983 (Box 7 (7-Research Files), Folder 30)
  - "Judicial Review" by Mark v. Tushnet, Undated (Box 7 (7-Research Files), Folder 31)
  - Judi- Crim meeting, 1985 (Box 7 (7-Research Files), Folder 32)
  - Jurisdiction-Deliquency, Volume IV of IX, ca. 1977 (Box 7 (7-Research Files), Folder 33)
  - "The Jurisdiction to do Justice: Florida's Jury Override and the State Constitution" by Michael Mello-Research, 1848; 1853; 1857-1858; 1876-1877; 1881-1882 (Box 7 (7-Research Files), Folder 34)
  - "The Jurisdiction to do Justice: Florida's Jury Override and the State Constitution" by Michael Mello-Research, 1891; 1894; 1896-1897; 1902; 1991 (Box 7 (7-Research Files), Folder 35)
  - "The Jurisdiction to do Justice: Florida's Jury Override and the State Constitution" by Michael Mello-Research, 1907-1908; 1924; 1926; 1937; 1960 (Box 7 (7-Research Files), Folder 36)
  - "The Jurisdiction to do Justice: Florida's Jury Override and the State Constitution" by Michael Mello-Research, 1963; 1966; 1968; 1972-1974; 1976-1977 (Box 7 (7-Research Files), Folder 37)
  - "The Jurisdiction to do Justice: Florida's Jury Override and the State Constitution" by Michael Mello-Research (1 of 4), 1979; 1990; 1992; Undated (Box 7 (7-Research Files), Folder 38)
  - "The Jurisdiction to do Justice: Florida's Jury Override and the State Constitution" by Michael Mello-Research (2 of 4), 1979-1990; 1992; Undated (Box 7 (7-Research Files), Folder 39)
  - "The Jurisdiction to do Justice: Florida's Jury Override and the State Constitution" by Michael Mello-Research (3 of 4), 1979-1990; 1992; Undated (Box 7 (7-Research Files), Folder 40)
  - "The Jurisdiction to do Justice: Florida's Jury Override and the State Constitution" by Michael Mello-Research (4 of 4), 1979-1990; 1992; Undated (Box 7 (7-Research Files), Folder 41)
  - "Jurisprudence and Gender" by Robin West, 1988 (Box 7 (7-Research Files), Folder 42)
  - "Jurisprudence and Legal Philosphy in Twentieth-Century America-Major Themes an Developments" by Martin P. Goulding, 1986 (Box 7 (7-Research Files), Folder 43)
  - Jurry Override, 1976; 1985-1990; 1992; Undated (Box 7 (7-Research Files), Folder 44)
  - "Justice After Trial: Prisoners' Need for Legal Services in the Criminal- Correctional Process" by Jacob and Sharma, 1970 (Box 7 (7-Research Files), Folder 45)
  - "Justice Black and Equal Protection" by Tinsley E. Yarbrough, 1977 (Box 7 (7-Research Files), Folder 46)
  - "Justice Black: Local Control and Federalism" by O'Rourke and Thernstrom, 1987 (Box 7 (7-Research Files), Folder 47)
  - "Justice Brennan and the Jurisprudence of Dissent" by Laura Krugman Ray, 1988 (Box 7 (7-Research Files), Folder 48)
  - "Justice Brennan, The Constitution and Modern American Liberalism" by David Rudenstine, 1988 (Box 7 (7-Research Files), Folder 49)
  - Justice Grants, 1992-1993 (Box 7 (7-Research Files), Folder 50)
  - "Justice Harlan" by Robert T. McCracken, 1912 (Box 7 (7-Research Files), Folder 51)
  - "Justice O'Conner on Executions", 2001 (Box 7 (7-Research Files), Folder 52)
  - "Justice Thurgood Marshall: Advocate for Human Need in American Jurisprudence" by William J. Brennan, JR., 1981 (Box 7 (7-Research Files), Folder 53)
  - Juvenile and Family Court Journal: The Juvenile Court and Serious Offenders 38 Recommendations, 1984 Summer (Box 8 (7-Research Files), Folder 1)
  - Juvenile and Family Courts by William H. Sheridan, 1984 (Box 8 (7-Research Files), Folder 2)
  - "The Juvenile Court and the Adversary system: Problems of Function and Form" by Joel F. Handler, 1965 (Box 8 (7-Research Files), Folder 3)
  - Juvenile Court Statistics 1984- U.S. Department of Justice, 1987 (Box 8 (7-Research Files), Folder 4)
  - "The Juvenile Death Penalty" by Warren M. Kato, 1997 (Box 8 (7-Research Files), Folder 5)
  - "The Juvenile Death Penalty: Counsel's Role in the Dependent of a Mitigation Defense" by Marla M. Homan, 1987 (Box 8 (7-Research Files), Folder 6)
  - "The Juvenile Death Penalty: In the Best Interests of the Child?" by Suzanne D. Strater, 1995 (Box 8 (7-Research Files), Folder 7)
  - "The Juvenile Death Penalty in Washington: A State Constitutional Analysis" by Bruce L. Brown, 1992 (Box 8 (7-Research Files), Folder 8)
  - "The Juvenile Death Penalty Today: Death Sentences and Executions for Juvenile Crimes, January 1, 1973-December 31, 2003" by Victor Sreib, 2004 (Box 8 (7-Research Files), Folder 9)
  - Juvenile Death Sentencing Statistics, Undated (Box 8 (7-Research Files), Folder 10)
  - Juvenile Deliquency by Clemens Bartallas- Excerpt, 1985 (Box 8 (7-Research Files), Folder 11)
  - Juvenile Executions in the United States since 1977- Amnesty International, 2004 (Box 8 (7-Research Files), Folder 12)
  - Juvenile Homicide Case Data, 1988 (Box 8 (7-Research Files), Folder 13)
  - "Juvenile Justice Reform: An Historical Perspective" by Sanford J. Fox, 1970 (Box 8 (7-Research Files), Folder 14)
  - Juvenile Justice Standards-Transfer between Courts-IJA-ABA Joint Commission, 1980 (Box 8 (7-Research Files), Folder 15)
  - "Juvenile Offenders Could Avoid Execution Florida May Join A National Trend and Strike the Death Penalty in Such Cases" by Maya Bell, 2004 (Box 8 (7-Research Files), Folder 16)
  - "Juvenile and the Death Penalty" by Lynn Cothern, 2000 (Box 8 (7-Research Files), Folder 17)
  - Juveniles and the Death Penalty- Experts, Undated (Box 8 (7-Research Files), Folder 18)
  - Juveniles Executed in Georgia since 1900, Undated (Box 8 (7-Research Files), Folder 19)
  - Keeney v. Tamayo-Reyes, 1992 (Box 8 (7-Research Files), Folder 20)
  - Kentucky Penal Code 532.025, 2004 (Box 8 (7-Research Files), Folder 21)
  - "Kids Who Kill: A Critique of How the American Legal System Deals with Juveniles who Commit Homicide" by Mirah A. Horowitz, 2000 (Box 8 (7-Research Files), Folder 22)
  - Knight v. Dugger, 1988 (Box 8 (7-Research Files), Folder 23)
  - Lanier v. Fairfield Communities Inc., 1990 (Box 8 (7-Research Files), Folder 24)
  - Lau v. Nichols, 1973-1974 (Box 8 (7-Research Files), Folder 25)
  - "Law and Gender: The Feminist Project in Action" by Kim Rosser, 1988 (Box 8 (7-Research Files), Folder 26)
  - "Law and Politics in the New Republic", 1966 (Box 8 (7-Research Files), Folder 27)
  - "Law as a moral Judgement vs. Law as the Rules of the Powerful" by Beyleveld and Brownsword, 1983 (Box 8 (7-Research Files), Folder 28)
  - LeCroy v. Florida, 1988 (Box 8 (7-Research Files), Folder 29)
  - LeCroy v. Florida, 1986 (Box 8 (7-Research Files), Folder 30)
  - Legal Positivism/ legal Realism- Hart/ Rogat, Undated (Box 8 (7-Research Files), Folder 31)
  - The Legal Status of Adolescents 1980- A Report of the Dept. of Health and Human Services ( 1 of 3), 1981 (Box 8 (7-Research Files), Folder 32)
  - The Legal Status of Adolescents 1980- A Review of the Dept. of Health and Human Services ( 2 of 3), 1981 (Box 8 (7-Research Files), Folder 33)
  - The Legal Status of Adolescents 1980- A Report of the Dept. of Health and Human Services (3 of 3), 1981 (Box 8 (7-Research Files), Folder 34)
  - Legislative Session- December, 1986; 1985-1986; Undated (Box 8 (7-Research Files), Folder 35)
  - Legislative Session-January- March 1986, Undated (Box 8 (7-Research Files), Folder 36)
  - Legislative Session- January- March 1987, Undated (Box 8 (7-Research Files), Folder 37)
  - Legislative Session-January-March 1988, Undated (Box 8 (7-Research Files), Folder 38)
  - Legislative Session- June 1987, Undated (Box 8 (7-Research Files), Folder 39)
  - Legislative Session-March 1986-January 1987, Undated (Box 8 (7-Research Files), Folder 40)
  - "Legislative Highlights of 1991" by Morty Rosenbaum, ca.1991 (Box 8 (7-Research Files), Folder 41)
  - "Legitimating Death" by Louis D. Bilionis, 1993 (Box 8 (7-Research Files), Folder 42)
  - "The Legitimation of Purposive Decisions" by Philipepe Nonet, 1980 (Box 8 (7-Research Files), Folder 43)
  - Lewis v. Florida, 1986 (Box 8 (7-Research Files), Folder 44)
  - Lewis v. Florida, 1991 (Box 8 (7-Research Files), Folder 45)
  - "The Life Span of a Judge-Made Rule" by John Paul Stevens, 1983 (Box 8 (7-Research Files), Folder 46)
  - Lindabury v. Landabury, 1988-1989 (Box 8 (7-Research Files), Folder 47)
  - List of Juveniles-Detailed Complaint Breakdown, 1988 (Box 8 (7-Research Files), Folder 48)
  - List of State Legislation Concerning Juveniles, 2004 (Box 8 (7-Research Files), Folder 49)
  - "Lon Fuller and Substantive Natural Law" by Anthony D' Amato, 1981 (Box 8 (7-Research Files), Folder 50)
  - "The Long Road up from Barbarism: Thurgood Marshall and the Death Penalty" by Jordan Streiker, 1993 (Box 8 (7-Research Files), Folder 51)
  - Long v. Florida, 1988 (Box 8 (7-Research Files), Folder 52)
  - Lozada v. Deeds, 1991 (Box 8 (7-Research Files), Folder 53)
  - Major Issues in Juvenile Justice Information and Training: Youth in Adult Courts: Between Two Worlds- U.S. Department of Justice ( 1 of 2), 1982 (Box 8 (7-Research Files), Folder 54)
  - Major Issues in Juvenile Justice Information and Training: Youth in Adult Courts: Between Two Worlds- U.S. Department of Justice ( 2 of 2), 1982 (Box 8 (7-Research Files), Folder 55)
  - Relentless Dissents- Marshall Papers ( 1 of 19), 1972-1993 (Box 8 (7-Research Files), Folder 56)
  - Relentless Dissents- Marshall Papers ( 2 of 19), 1972-1993 (Box 8 (7-Research Files), Folder 57)